Can I turn on music?
No problem, turn on
Anything, but rap
What music is this?
Ah, it's you doing this?
You don't say!
May I film you, bro?
You are so
Wait a sec
Wait a sec my guy!
Usually, I don't like this
but damn it's nice to hear this
Oppa, brotha's spitting fire
like crazy
Can you make it again?
My goodness!
Nice one!
Cmon, a goody, a goody
It's forward
It's incorrect?
Forward
That's good
Nice one
My gosh
Is it a program or what?
No, just lips
And what's this?
Just a microphone
You don't say!
1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 1, 1, 1
My goodness!
Low five!
Is it your feature?
Something ike that
Drive'n'entertain people
Fudge, you're cool
I like you
And I didn't get it
from the start
It's like music started
And after I saw it
I'm like "naaah"
And you said
"Can I turn on music?"
You heard on the Internet
something like that?
I've never heard
First time?
Yes
That's cool
You don't mind
if I turn on music?
Nah, it's OK, turn on
It was you?
Nice one!
Thank you
It was very
beautiful, seriously
Thank you
Did you think
it was music playing?
Do you know more or
only this song?
Actually, I've got
more songs
Well done, brother
Thanks
Можете отметить меня,
если загрузите в Инстаграм?
Oh, 30 thousands
Well done
Thanks
Can I turn on music?
I don't care
You can turn on
It's better with music
I am always on
the wheel myself
Awesome!
How do you like this
kind of music?
Have you ever heard
something like this?
I don't even know
A human orchestra
they call it
We try to imitate
sounds of music
Usually drum sounds
We didn't have this
back in my days
Can I turn on music?
You know better
No sh#t
Well executed
I thought at the start
there are speakers
Then I look at you
A beatboxer?
Yes! Beatbox!
It's called beatbox
I am gladly surprised
people know
that it is beatbox and all this
is called beatbox
Young people know
Can I turn on music?
I'm a robot
I must
must
I'm a dummy robot
I must dance
A dummy robot
How do you like this music?
Awesome
It seems I've seen you before
To be honest,
I am a Russian beatbox champion
Current
Yes?
Yes
I came about
three months ago
Maybe that's why
you've seen me somewhere
Now you'll stop here?
Yet here, maybe
I'll go to Almaty next month