That's it! Quiet!
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Beatbox?
Yes
May I ask you a question?
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Yes
I do it and I'd like
to perform you something
Let's go
Can I film you?
You can film
I've made a song about my cat
For you to rate
Will you film?
♫ I like cats, ♫
♫ To pet them and to scratch ♫
♫ It's not gross to me ♫
♫ To clean up their crap ♫
♫ But my cat escaped ♫
♫ Now I'm really sad ♫
♫ For not to be sad ♫
♫ I'll go and find him ♫
♫ Where's the cat? ♫
♫ Where's ♫
♫ The cat? ♫
So cool!
Thank you
Cool, cool
Nice one
How's the song?
Cool song
You've lost the cat?
Yes
I've lost
That's all
The cat ran away from me
Have you heard live
beatbox before?
Live? No
First time?
Yes
It's nice
How long do you do it?
For about 15 years
For 15 years?
Amazing
You've reacted very cool,
to be honest
Because, usually,
Especially, when elder people sit
They don't understand
what's happening
Who's donig what
They probably don't know
what's beatbox
I explain to them firstly
I say "There's that and that"
Many people are just shy
Maybe, when I started doing
into the microphone
The contrast
Yes!
It was cool
I thougth
You make such a vibration
Let me to don't talk
Can I film you for Stories?
Yes
Cool
Thank you
Nice one
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Yes
I do it and I'd like to show
you something
To demonstrate
Maybe, I'm able to surprise you
🤖 I'm a robot 🤖
🤖 I must 🤖
🤖 Must 🤖
🤖 I'm a dummy robot 🤖
🤖 I must dance 🤖
🤖 A dummy robot 🤖
🤖 Must dance 🤖
🤖 I must dance 🤖
Cool
Thanks
For how long you do it?
For about 15 years
Really cool
Do you film videos for YouTube?
I film
How many subscribers do you have?
55 thousands
Actually, I film you as well
And if you don't mind,
I'll upload you to YouTube
Upload it
You can find and watch yourself
later
What to search?
What's the device there?
I just do music,
Show everyone my talent
to people I drive
I can show you too,
if you don't mind
No problems
♫ How are you? ♫
♫ Amazing ♫
♫ I'm crazy amazing ♫
Can you turn it off?
Done. You can continue
♫ How are you? ♫
♫ Amazing ♫
♫ We're crazy amazing ♫
♫ We are all amazing ♫
♫ And crazy amazing ♫
♫ How are you? ♫
♫ Amazing ♫
♫ We're crazy amazing ♫
♫ We are all amazing ♫
Cool
Thank you
Actually, it's very, very fine
Thank you very much
Do you know what is beatbox?
Yes
I'd like to perform you,
I'm doing it for quite long
Let's go
It's
powerful vibrations
Good sound there, you feel it?
Yes, a lot
The whole body was vibrating
You can also work
in night clubs
In a night club? Don't know.
I haven't tried yet.
- You know, VIP service
- Maybe, I should try
You need to take extra
money for this
I'll tell my director
to write a review
Thank you
On Yandex
You can, you know what?
Make people reactions on TikTok
As I already do
I wanted to tell you right now,
that I film you
You film us?
Yes
Where?
My whistle is also there?
Everything is there
If you don't mind I'll upload you
You can watch yourselves
on YouTube later
You can type "Improver"
On YouTube?
Yes, on YouTube
Listen, do you know what is beatbox?
No
It's when music made with lips
and mouth
Maybe ever heard?
On TikTok
No
It's like
Have you heard
something like this?
No, I don't watch TikTok at all
You don't say
I just do beatbox and
I'd like to show you something
To perform beatbox
Maybe I'll be able
to surprise you
What do you think about it?
Actually, it is surprising
Surprising?
Can I perform something longer?
A more completed piece
Ok?
Well
Fine
That's it! Quiet!
Why?
What's this? You're scared?
Why do you have a microphone here?
You've got scared?
No taxi has a microphone
And I have one
You work as a tiktok and
a taxi driver?
Yes
I have a channel on TikTok
Ah, I get it
So what?
My friend,
that is in Astana, also
films TikToks
When I come to him, we film
You film a TikTok?
Not really a tiktok
What do you film?
Well
You should ask my friend
about this
Let's go and film
a video on TikTok
With me
I'm not really can make a tiktok
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
👴 Hallo! I don't understand
🤖 1, 2, 3, I'm a robot
Stop it! Everyone will hear us and
No one can hear us
Only you can hear me
and nobody else
Why?
😈 Only you can hear me!
And why?
🤖 Because we're in a car
Again a wrong way?
No, it's a correct way!
Where to go next?
Go back!
Back? Why to go back?
Go back
This way, to go left, isn't it?
No, go back
Where to go?
There is the house
I couldn't know this
And you didn't tell
Go back
Oopsie-doopsie
Tell me where to go
Go this way, this way, this way,
this way
We let the car go by
That's all, it's gone
We are breaking through!
It seems, it's a wrong way
I don't know, again
arrived to a wrong place
We're breaking through then
We can't break throguh,
we're not in a tank
Then go back again
Go back again
I got it!
We have only two ways
Where?
We could go from there
or from there
Between this orange and
that black skyscraper
That's an intersting thing
you came up with
Here it is, here it is,
here it is
It seems we've arrived
That's all, have a good one!