- Hello
- May I ask you a question?
- Yes
Do you know what beatbox is?
I just started practicing it recently
and I want to show you something to rate me
Because I am yet afraid to show it
to the big audience
You know... I am not a specialist
And I need an opinion of a regelar
listener
- Let's go then...
- How it is listenable
Let's go then
That's so cool
You need to do it, and if you started
recently
You're very talented
Amazing, so classy
Thank you :)
Well done
Thank you very much
- Hello
How do you know what door to drive to?
You wrote it, don't you?
Ahah, no
We saw that you are coming
What the #@%k?
Listen, I hear the sound like it's
coming out of speakers
Well, he speaks, yeah
As I speak, do you hear me in the back?
I hear a bit too much
Like in a plane
- Yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah
- Like in a plane. Why?
I did it on purpose for me
to sound better
And I thought for me to hear better
And for you to hear better
I thought I've got something
with my head
And with someone's next
I think I'm already on a plane
Let me show something,
I am a musician after all
Let's go
But we are almost arrived
It's exactly two minutes left
Let's go, let's go, there is
a long traffic light in front of us
That's fun
It's like an physiotherapy for an
asthmatic?
Well, yes
It helps me, btw
What instrument did you do?
Drums
And vocals of course
- I think, yes
- Can't belive, I can't belive
I've seen something like this
only on the TV
It's like an orchestra man
Hello
We're ordering a pizza
Come on, come on, more
♪We're ordering a pizza!♪
Amazing!
Wow, that's amazing!
Thank you!
A vehicle audio is useless here
May I ask you a question?
Do you know what beatbox is?
Noo
It's when a music made with lips
and mouth
Maybe ever heard?
Yes, I did.
I just ride and entertain
people a little bit
Maybe you can hear me
also in the back?
Yes
I wanted to try something and
maybe I'll surprise you
Let's go
That's so cool I am shocked!
And why... Why are you still here?
You need to go further,
somewhere bigger. So cool!
Thank you
Very talented! Can't believe it
I heard it of course,
but this much cool - never
Really never heard
- Thank you very much, very pleasant
- It's so cool
- Hello
- May I ask you a question?
- Mhm
Do you know what beatbox is?
Well, I heard. And why are you
speaking into mic?
I want to perform you beatbox,
I started doing it recently
that's why I've plugged
a special mic
- Just to sing beatbox?
- Just to sing beatbox, yeah
Wow, let's try then
Oh my! Cool!
That's cool! I liked it
Is it your hobby?
Well, yes, you can say
I do it professionally
on some level.
Because I perform sometime
When I sat and understood
that you are speaking into mic
I thought "Why are you speaking
into mic?". Weird.
And the camera of the phone
pointed this way
was a little bit confusing
I thought "What is this hidden
camera?"
Can I see your microphone?
You won't see it because
it's right here
on the neck
I've connected it there
Hello
May I ask you a question?
Yes
Do you know what beatbox is?
What?
Do you know what is beatbox?
I just started doing it
not so long ago
And I want to perform you something,
if you don't mind
For you to rate. Huh?
I don't mind
Awesome
Awesome!
Is it really you?
I've got a mic also
Maybe you can hear that you hear
me there as I speak
Yes, I hear
It's like, you know, it's like
some music started
It's really like a recording has
started
That's cool
And you do it professionally?
Well, yes
And you win something maybe?
I am a Russian beatbox champion,
to be honest
Of Russia?
Can't believe it
Astonishing
Wow, that's fun
Thank you very much
I am glad you liked it
And I was like
"Is it really a human voice?"