OH F*CK!
Can I turn on music?
Yes, of course, you can
Wow, you're the only
one who asked
OH F*CK!
I'm shocked
F*ck!
How do you like such music?
It's really lit!
I'm leaving a like
and approving this
Strongly approving
Do you mind if I turn on
music a bit?
No problem
How do you like such music?
I don't understand
It was you or what?
I even got lost
Yes, I have a mic
attached to the neck
And I can make it
louder and quieter
My gosh
I thought, when you asked
about music,
that the sound
is from speakers
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Astonishing
Do you mind if I'll
turn on music a bit?
No, we don't
Awesome!
You're doing it great
I'm sorry, I filmed you
Thank you
It's like a car ra...
It's like a car radio
Thanks
You are so creative
Yeah, gotta uplift
people's mood
How's the genre called?
I can do lotta things
It is called beatbox
Yes, beatbox
Feels like a speaker beats
Well done
Amazing!
Thank you
Welcome
Can I turn on music?
You do it yourself?
It's cool
Well done
How do you do it?
It's called beatbox
Beatbox?
Yes
We beatboxers
imitate sounds of music
Awesome, yeah
You're awesome
Thank you
A drum set has a kick drum
The first sound
The second sound is a hat
The third sound is
a snare drum
And here I have
Can we do it again
from the start?
Let me think what to do
So cool
What's your name?
My name is Vanya
Ivan
This is a talent
You can also find me
on the Internet
If you want to
I'm being published
there sometimes
Here is Instagram
OK
OK, thank you
Thank you too,
have a nice day!
All the best
Goodbye