- Hello
May I ask you a question?
- Yes
- Of course
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Yes
I just do it for a little
and want to show you something.
See, I have a mic attached and
you can hear me in the back, don't you?
Yes, indeed
Perfectly hear
I'll make something. You don't mind?
Yes, we don't mind
Wow! Amazing! Is it real?
- Really cool!
- Really powerful!
Just *applauses*
Thank you very much
I don't regret I sat on
the front seat
Thank you very much.
Such an amazing reaction!
It is really cool
It is reaaally cool
It seems you do it
profesionally, don't you?
Well, yes. Maybe, for about 15 years
Wowzer! Now i get it
Wow, such a lucky ride
Have you ever heard something like this?
No, only on the internet, never live
Maybe, that's why you have
such a reaction
Maybe
Really powerful, very cool
Thank you very much
You know, you can go on a talent show
Well, yes, I would go
Do you have some of them
in Kazakhstan?
I just came from Russia recently
I get it then
Will we see ourselves semewhere?
If you want, I can add you
to the video. If you don't mind.
You can even find me and
watch yourselves later
On Insta?
No, on Youtube
You have 43K subscribers! Oh my!
I'm subscribing. I subscribed now
Thank you
Amazing
Oh my god, it's here, right?
Hi, everyone!
I'll come
A celebration or something?
Kinda
Or vice versa?
yeah, vice versa
What happend?
Well, everything is fine
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Bimox?
Beat. Box.
Beatbox?
Yeah
Don't know
Never ever heard?
I'm 47... 50
When music is made with lips.
Heard it?
Yeah
Drums and stuff
Ah... The three, the three...
One person makes music
with no instruments
Actually, it was three of them
I do beatbox and want to show you
something
For you to listen
I... do not ardfwst...
Huh?
I don't argue with that
May I show you something, yeah?
Of course
Oh my gosh
It's strong... I agree
Cool, cool
Seriously speaking, very cool
Huh, f*ck...
Not a lot of people here swim out,
actually
Actually speaking,
there is only one life
And it's a fight
No, and what?
Fudge, it's cool
Thank you
Seriously speaking, a nice one
Like...
F*ck...
Well done
You can
Thanks
All the best, have a nice day!
Ouch, you're shocking me again
Have a nice one!
I can, I can
Best of luck
Thank you
Hello
May I ask you a question?
Do you know, what is beatbox?
When music is made with lips.
Maybe ever heard once?
No
On TikTok
I just do it and
I want to perform you something
You can hear in the back I have
a mic attached
Can you hear me?
One, two, three, four...
And I want to perform you something,
maybe I'll manage to surprise you
Maybe to uplift your mood
Yes, let's go
I'll check the sound
You can hear me well there?
- Cool
Thanks
Have you ever heard something
like this live?
Live? No
Only on the Internet, yes?
Yes
It is very cool
Thank you
Honestly, I make videos and if you
don't mind, I'll add you
How you are reacting
On TikTok?
On YouTube. You can find there
and watch later, if you want
On YouTube just type "Improver"
In English
Are you self-taught or have
been studying somewhere?
I do it for about 15 years
Since the very young age. I heard
how they do it, and tried to
replicate it
from video
Even became campion of Russia
Why don't you record a track?
Do you mean self composed song
with beatbox?
Actually, I have songs I made
myself with beatbox, like
Cool
It should be nice to dance to it
Yeah, a dance club one
Hello
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Beatbox?
Yes
Maybe ever heard a word once?
I heard a word, but don't know
what is it
When a person with his mouth and
his speech apparatus
makes music. Maybe heard it?
On TikTok maybe
Ahh, got it, yes-yes
I just started doing it
And I wonder, how it is listenable
by another person
Will I surprise you or not?
Let me perform you something
And you will tell me
if it's fine or not
Usually, young people are
interested in this
You call yourself an old man
too early
I am 60 in two years
It's amazing
You look young, don't look your age.
It should be,
everyone say this to you
I'll make something?
Let's go
Yes. Impressing
How much breath it takes
Yes, long years of training
How do you do all this?
If you break it down into steps,
Then, as in every
kind of art, for example,
fighters perfects a basic punch,
a dancer - basic moves
If you want to learn a language,
you need to learn its alphabet,
And here the same
You need to know basic sounds,
percussive sounds
It's a kick, the biggest drum,
a hi-hat, that we hit,
and a small drum that sounds like
Having these three sounds
allowing us make some rythms
It's only three sounds
How's that all called?
How have you said?
How's this all called?
What is it, you have said?
Beatbox
Hello
Salam
Why is it so loud?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1, 2
What does it mean?
I just have a mic attached
Ah, s&*t, I got scared
Gosh, you make jokes
I think "A special department maybe"
Actually, I do beatbox.
Do you know what is this?
Ah! Yes
I am Russian beatbox champion
You don't say!
And we can even listen to it?
It's all here for a reason
As I thought
And you go
"Turn it off, turn it off"
Bro, may I record?
You may record
Gosh! You don't say!
I will post it, and everyone will
"Sheesh, you are with the beatbox world champ"
You start?
Who are you?
Amazing
Gosh you're lit
Oh my God, bro!
I pressed on photo, you know