Do you know what is beatbox?
Yes, a bit
I'm practicing, and I'd like
to show you something
How I do it
and you could rate it
Yes, let's go
Well done, well done
Thank you
Do you know what is beatbox?
Maybe ever heard once
When music is made with lips?
I've just started
practicing it recently
and I'd like to make something
for you
If you don't mind
Let's go
Powerful
Thank you
Hello
Why does your voice
sounds so strange?
How strange?
It sounds like a dubbed voice
It's just a joke
I'm driving and having fun
Do you know what is beatbox?
Yes
I'm a beatboxer
a good one
And I can perform you something,
if you want
Let's go
I've written a song
about my cat
My cat escaped
And I'm really upset
I wrote a song
♫ I like cats ♫
♫ To pet them and to scratch ♫
♫ It's not gross to me ♫
♫ To clean up their crap ♫
♫ But my cat's escaped ♫
♫ Now I'm really sad ♫
♫ For not to be sad ♫
♫ I'll go and find him ♫
♫ Where's the cat? ♫
It's funny
Thank you
I'm also a musician
Do you play something?
I've finished Choir Directing
I play piano and sing
Now I study
Higher Pop & Jazz Singing
What a twist!
Maybe you can sing something
and I'll make beatbox
I don't even know, I'm scared
Cool!
Awesome!
Really well done
Do you know what is beatbox?
I don't
Maybe ever heard when music's
made with lips?
Without instruments
With lips?
I'm practicing it. And I'd
like to show you something
Maybe I'll uplift your mood
Awesome!
First time hearing!
Do you know what is beatbox?
I'm practicing it and I'd like
to perform you something
Interesting,
if I can surprise you
Let's go
Oh my! Awesome!
Did you like it?
First time in my life
I'm listening to beatbox
Amazing, it's cool
For how long do you do it?
For about 15 years
Awesome
Right from the chorus
Cool!
Awesome!
Do you know what is beatbox?
Beatbox? Yes
While we're in a traffic jam
I'm a beatboxer
A good one
I can make something for you
Really?
Maybe I'll uplift your mood
Let's go
It was astonishing
Thank you very much
Such a talant!
Thank you
I didn't expect the flex
with a microphone
Unexpected plot twist
When I pulled out a mic
Thank you
Do you make songs remixes
more often or self-composed?
I have self-composed as well
People like remixes more
because they hear
familiar track
and go "Ohh that's the piece,
I know that"
start dancing,
give a better reaction
I have my own song,
I can make it right now
Yes, let's go
It's powerful! Damn
It's hard
Thank you
I like it a lot
I think it's hard
to sit to these beats
No chances
It starts craving to do like
Some instincts?
Yeah instincts
I can't help myself
Gice me a fist bump
That's it
Thank you for the mood
Thank you either
Good bye!