Hello!
How's your New Year's mood?
It's very good
The thing is,
I'm a Santa's Helper
He told me to uplift
people's moods in a taxi
And I've decided to sing
Christmas songs
Do you mind if I'll
sing you something?
No
Here was a routine
Awesome!
Do you know how it's called?
Beatbox?
Beatbox, yes!
I have a bag with presents
And you have a unique
opportunity
to get one of these presents
If you'll try
to repeat something
from what I did
Let's try
Let's try together with me
That's it, excellent!
You've deserved a present
From Santa Claus
Just put your hand there
Ohhh, thank you
And yours is red
Thank you
Happy New Year!
And you too
Thanks
Hello
Give me please
your phone number
In honor of the New Year
all rides are free
Today all rides are free
in honor of the New Year
Today's free?!
Santa Claus has already paid
for everything
Actually, I'm his helper
He told me to drive
and uplift people's mood
in a taxi
Thank you!
Here it is
I'd like to sing
a Christmas song for you
Let's go
Oi thank you!
Thank you very much!
Happy New Year's Eve!
And you too!
He also told me
To give you a gift
For the New Year
Who told you?!
Santa Claus! Who else?
You don't say!
Of course! I told you,
I'm his helper
He wants to give
you these balls
Oi thank you very much!
Nice balls for
your Christmas tree
I'll put them there.
Thank you very much
You're welcome
Happy New Year's Eve!
I wish you health, wealth
and happiness
Millions in the New Year
And I wish you all too!
Thanks!
Hello
How's your New Year's mood?
Good, good
The thing is
I'm not a regular taxist
I'm a Santa Claus helper
He told me to uplift
people's moods in a taxi
And I'd like to sing you
a Christmas song
If you don't mind
I don't mind
It's lit, really lit
Did I manage to uplift
New Year's mood?
Yes-yes-yes
You have a unique opportunity
to recieve a gift from Santa Claus
Today
If you'll repeat any beat
From what I just did
What was there?
That's it!
Excelllent
It was good for me
Chocolate sweets
You'll have a tea
with milk
As Santa likes
Happy New Year's Eve!
And you too!
Thanks
Good Evening, good evening
Who wants presents?
Sweeties like this,
here you go
Somebody needs a snowman?
Are you gifting?
Yes, I've got presents
Are you drunk?
Does Santa
happen to be drunk?
Let's go have a photo
Let's go
Have a good one!
Hello, grandson, hello
You didn't recognize me?
I am Santa Claus!
I'd like to give you a gift
Will you sing me a song or
tell me a poem?
I don't have any?
You can't?
Let me sing you something
Nice one
Look
If you'll repeat anything
from what I just showed you
I'll gift you a present
Will you?
Nah, thanks
The most simple
Let's go
Let's go more, a bit longer
Excellent!
Excellent job you did!
And you said, you can't
Look here
Here's a snowman for you
To create New Year's mood
Thank you
You'll put it next to
your Christmas tree
You're welcome
Happy New Year's Eve
And you too
Wish you happiness, health
and love
Thank you
Hello
Hello, hello, granddaughter
So awesome
It's so nice to go with
Santa Claus
Tell me granddaughter
how you behaved this year
Good
All amazing
How's your New Year's mood
New Year's mood? It's okay.
Okay?
Let me sing you
a Christmas song
To uplift your mood
Let's go
May I film?
Yes
Here's a little song
Wow, cool, awesome,
Thank you Santa Claus
for the song
Welcome
Uplifted the mood
Happy New Year's Eve
I felt the New Year's coming
after your song
Here's a little lamp for you
A gift
Oh thank you! For what?
Thank you Santa Claus
for the gift!
For what? For no reason
It's very pleasant,
thank you
Welcome
Wish you happiness, health, love
And all the best wishes
in the New Year
Thank you and to you as well
Thank you
The main wish is
to stay healthy
Thank you, my girl,
thank you
If you'll be healthy,
you'll be anything you wish
It is true
The main thing
And a great mood in
the New Year
I also sing songs
You what?!
Yes
Cute little fir tree
Is freezing in the cold
Take it from forest,
It is warm at home
Hand in hand in circle
Cheerful and happy
I've really forgotten
Hello, Sara!
Hello, Vanya!
I was looking exactly
for you!
We need to sing a song
for the boys and girls!
About the Christmas tree!
Are you ready?
I'm ready!
Let's go!
There was a Fir-Tree
born in woods
And there she was grown,
In winter and in summer both
The grace and green she was
The snow around the thicky woods
Is creaking under skid
A shaggy Gee-Gee frisks ahead
In greatest rush indeed
The Gee-Gee's carrying firewoods
On them there is a Man
He chopped down our little Fir
At the very rootlet
And now in gallant here she is
On feast to us she came
And many many joyances
All little kids she gave
Wait a second we
have to film something
Something?
Yeah, wait a little bit
Here's a gift for you
Amazing!
Thank you!
Wish you happiness,
health and love!
And all the best wishes to you!