♫ To clean up their crap ♫
♫ But my cat esc... ♫
Hello
May I ask you a question?
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Yes
I'm just doing it
and I'd like to try to surprise you
What do you think about it?
To show something
What I can
Yes, you may
So cool
Thanks
Did I manage to surprise?
Yes, a lot!
Especially at the end
It's when I started doing fast?
Yes-yes-yes
Cool
It means, you like faster music
maybe, yes?
Yes, most likely
Is it a microphone there?
Yes, I have here
Attached to the neck,
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
I didn't understand at the start
I thought at the start, that
Some robot is speaking
I'm a robot
When you said hello
Hello
May I ask you a question?
Yes, I'm listening to you
Can you hear me in the back
on the speaker?
Yes
I just do beatboxing
Do you know, what is beatbox?
Yes
And I'd like to show you somehing
I am just interested
if I can surprise you or not
I've made a song about my cat
Can you imagine?
♫ I like cats ♫
♫ To pet them and to scratch ♫
♫ It's not gross to me ♫
♫ To clean up their crap ♫
♫ But my cat escaped ♫
♫ Now I'm really sad ♫
♫ For not being sad ♫
♫ I'll go and find him ♫
♫ Where's the cat? ♫
♫ Where's ♫
♫ The cat ♫
Powerful
Seriously, you do it yorself?
It seems that way because
I have a microphone connected
Thank you
Cool
Really powerful
I'm impressed
A few days back
I installed subwoofer
A big one speaker in the back
Now
Basses
Cool
Unusual
Thank you very much
You really uplifted me
Nice
May I ask you a question?
Do you know, what is beatbox?
No, don't know
Maybe you heard when
Music made with lips
With no instruments
No, didn't hear
Like, drums
No, I didn't hear
I just started doing it recently
I'd like to show you something
No, no need, I'm afraid
Afraid?!
Why?
Why the sound is like that?
I've made this on purpose
Are you from Russia?
Yes
Adorable
I got it from the start
We have a bit different guys
Our guys wouldn't do this
Why?
You're modern, you see
And ours...
Firstly, ours would be shy to show
You know, I have a friend
from Karaganda
He's such a beatboxer
He's beatboxing even better than me
(Check sp4rk on YouTube)
That's why you're wrong
Yes?
Let me make something
to surprise a little bit
You can try
a quick one
Road police here,
for some reason
Turn right on the traffic light
OK
Damn
Are you learning somewhere?
I've already learned
Actually
Huh?
What is it here?
A microphone somewhere?
Yes, I have here
1, 2, 3, 4, 1, Oppa
That's why you have
the echo here
Yes
Like this
Thank you
You're welcome
Have a nice evening
- Best of luck
- Thank you too
Did you like it?
Will you do like this?
Or you can dance only?
May I ask you a question?
You may
Do you know what is beatbox?
I heard of it, yes
I'd like to show you something
I do beatbox
Interesting, if I can surprise you?
I connected a microphone
specially for this
I get it
Don't mind if I'll make something?
Let's go
Cool
Thank you very much
And all this goes to YouTube?
Yes, and if you don't mind
I'll upload the clip with you
Should be funny
Hello
May I ask you a question?
Yes, of course
Do you know what is beatbox?
Of course, I do
Why "of course"?
Because I do music myself
Beatbox?
Not beatbox
It seems you're recording
Well, I... Actually, yes
- I got it from the start
- Well, I don't drive without
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, oppa, damn
I'd like to perform something
No problems
It's nice, nice one
Have you tried recording?
Yes, I record
Upload to YouTube
Some routines
Thank you
I own a little record studio
Seriously?
No words
What a
- Coincidence
I got it from the start
I see, a phone turned this way
can't be for no reason
I installed subwoofer recently
It goes hard
Earlier I was recording
without subwoofer
The sound was so-so
There was lack of lows
The only thing is
Distortion occurs
Nothing to do with this.