Hello
From this side
Do you know what is beatbox?
Maybe ever heard?
No, to be honest
Or maybe you've heard when with help
of mouth or speech apparatus
people make music with no instruments
Ah, yes, I'm recalling something
I do it regullary
I'd like to show something
Maybe I'll manage to surprise you
Yes
I have a microphone connected
specially for this
I'm sitting and seeing like
"a microphone?"
Cool
No, really
It's well done
Is it only your accompaniment?
Yes-yes
Cool, I even recorded on video
It is really just a mic amplifies,
I mean
without a microphone
I see
Hello
Do you know what is beatbox?
What?
I don't even know
Maybe you've ever heard when
Music is made with mouth
and no instruments
Yes
I've just started doing it
And I'd like to show you something
For you to rate
If it's listenable from aside
I've even connected the mic
for this
Let's go
It was cool
Yes
Really cool
Thank you
Did I manage to surprise?
Yes
Really cool
Can you do it again?
Something else?
Yes
So cool
Thank you
Cool
Do you know what is beatbox?
Beatbox?
Is it when
music is made with mouth?
In short, I do it
I'd like to show something
Maybe I can surprise you
Let's go
Very cool
Thank you
It's like really well done
Thanks
Do you know what is beatbox?
Beatbox?
Do you know?
No, I don't
I do it and I'd like
to make something
Let's go
Super
Cool
Thank you
May I turn on music?
Of course!
You may even talk with us
I usually talk a lot
I'll make music myself
With mouth
Do you know what is beatbox?
We know
I liked it all
Yes
It's actually very cool
I just didn't get
how's a microphone there
How?
Like that
1, 2, 3,
1, 2, 3, 4, 5
Ok, now I get it
I didn't see it from the start
Are your speakers boosted?
I have a subwoofer
installed there
As I thought there's something
installed in the back
Yes, it's like
Do you perform somewhere
in Karaganda?
No. I didn't perform even once